Preliminary Guide to the William Henry Bishop Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, 1841-1930, undated; Accession 2012-M-035
  - Manuscripts, drafts, and notes
    - Miscellaneous magazine articles, reviews, and newspaper clippings of Bishop's work with his annotations, 1875-1922 (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
    - Miscellaneous manuscript notes and literary scraps, 1879-1907, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Notebooks
    - Notes and sketches, 1878 September (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Titles, suggestions for stories, etc., and literary memoranda, 1884, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1875-1893, undated (Box 7, Folder 3-5)
  - Specifications for bank and office building, Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)